<resources>
    <string name="app_name">How To Cook That 2</string>
    <string name="scrambledEggs">
    \tIngredients\n\n

    \t\t4 fresh large eggs\n
    \t\tCooking spray, butter, or oil\n
    \t\tSalt and pepper to taste (optional)\n\n\n

    \tInstructions\n\n

    1. Coat the pan and heat over medium-low heat.\n\n

    2. Crack the eggs into a bowl, add a pinch of\n
    salt, and whisk until well blended.\n\n

    3. Pour in the eggs and immediately use a spatula\n
    to swirl in small circles around the pan until\n
    the eggs look slightly thickened and small curds\n
    begin to form - about 30 seconds.\n\n

    4. Switch from circles to making long sweeps across\n
    the pan until you see larger, creamy curds - \n
    20 seconds.\n\n

    5. Once the eggs are softly set and slightly runny,\n
    remove the pan from the heat and leave for a few\n
    seconds to finish cooking. Give a final stir, \n
    season to taste, and serve.\n\n

    6. Enjoy :)</string>

    <string name="friedEggs">
\tIngredients\n\n

    \t\t1 fresh egg\n
    \t\tCooking spray, butter, or oil\n
    \t\tSalt and pepper to taste (optional)\n\n\n

\tInstructions\n\n

    1. Coat pan and heat over medium heat.\n\n

    2. Crack the egg into a bowl and drop the egg\n
       in the pan.\n\n

    3. Let the egg cook until white is set and the\n
       corners begin to curl - about 3-4 minutes.\n
       For sunny-side up, slide the egg onto a plate\n
       and season. For over-easy or over-medium eggs,\n
       continue to Step 4.\n\n

    4. Using a thin spatula, jiggle it under the egg\n
       and flip. Allow to cook for about another minute\n
       for over-easy and 2 minutes for over-medium.\n\n

    5. Season the egg to taste and serve.\n\n

    6. Enjoy :)\n\n</string>

    <string name="porkLoin">
\tIngredients\n\n

    \t\tBoneless pork LOIN (not tenderloin)\n
    \t\t1 tablespoon olive oil\n
    \t\t1/2 tablespoon salt\n
    \t\t1/2 tablespoon pepper\n
    \t\t1/2 tablespoon garlic powder\n
    \t\t1/2 tablespoon onion powder\n\n\n

\tInstructions\n\n

    1. Preheat oven to 400 degrees Fahrenheit.\n\n

    2. Rub pork with all the ingredients on all sides\n\n

    3. Place pork in roasting pan fat side up\n\n

    4. Cook at 400 degrees Fahrenheit for 10 minutes\n\n

    5. Lower heat to 350 F and cook for 20 minutes\n
        PER POUND (~42 minutes for 2.08 pound pork loin)\n\n

    6. Check that it has reached an internal temperature of at\n
        least 145 degrees Fahrenheit and remove from oven\n\n

    7. Loosely place a piece of foil over the roast and\n
        let sit for 10 minutes\n\n

    8. Transfer to (meat) cutting board to slice for serving\n\n

    9. Enjoy :)</string>
    <string name="porkChops">
\tIngredients\n\n

    \t\tFor the brine (optional):\n
    \t\t\t3 cups cold water\n
    \t\t\t3 tablespoons kosher salt\n
    \t\t\t(or 2 1/2 tablespoons of table salt)\n
    \t\tOption flavorings:\n
    \t\t\t2 smashed garlic cloves\n
    \t\t\t1/2 teaspoon black peppercorns\n
    \t\t\t1 bay leaf\n
    \t\tFor the pork chops:\n
    \t\t\t2-4 Bone-in pork chops\n
    \t\t\tOlive oil\n
    \t\t\tSalt and pepper\n\n

\tInstructions\n\n

    1. Brine the pork chops (optional). Bring 1 cup\n
       of water to a boil, add the salt and optional\n
       flavorings, and stir to dissolve the salt. Add\n
       2 more cups of water to bring the temperature\n
       of the brine down to room temperature. Place\n
       the pork chops in a shallow dish and pour. The\n
       brine should cover the chops. Cover and put in\n
       the fridge for 30 minutes or up to 4 hours.\n\n

    2. Heat the oven and the skillet. Heat to 400°F.\n
       Place a large oven-safe skillet in the oven to\n
       heat as well.\n\n

    3. Season the pork chops. Remove them from the \n
       brine. If you didn\'t brine, that\'s fine. Remove\n
       the pork chops from their packaging. Pat dry with\n
       paper towels. Rub both sides with olive oil, then\n
       season with salt and pepper.\n\n

    4. Remove the skillet from the oven. CAREFULLY\n
       remove the skillet and set it over medium-high\n
       heat on the stovetop. Turn on a vent fan or open\n
       a window. (It\'s about to get smokey!).\n\n

    5. Sear the pork chops. Place the pork chops in the\n
        hot skillet. Sear until the bottom of the chops are\n
        golden-brown, about 3 minutes. Turn down the heat\n
        if it gets too smokey.\n\n

    6. Flip the chops over and transfer to the oven. Use\n
       tongs to flip the chops. Using oven mitts, place the\n
       skillet in the oven.\n\n

    7. Roast the chops until cooked through. They\n
       should register 140°F to 145°F in the thickest part\n
       of the meat. Cooking time will be 6 to 10 minutes\n
       depending on the thickness of chops, how cool they\n
       were at the start of cooking, and whether they were\n
       brinned. Start checking the chops at 6 minutes and\n
       continue checking every minute or two until they are\n
       ready.\n\n

    8. Rest the chops. Transfer the chops onto a plate\n
       and pour any pan juices over the top. Tent loosely\n
       with foil and let the chops rest for at least 5\n
       minutes before serving.\n\n

    9. Enjoy :)</string>
    <string name="spamBowl">
\tIngredients\n\n

    \t\t2 cups white sushi rice\n
    \t\t~1/2 small avocado - diced\n
    \t\t1 can Spam - diced small\n
    \t\tScallions for garnish\n
    \t\tFurikake for garnish (optional)\n\n
    \t\tSpam sauce:\n
        \t\t1/4 cup oyster sauce\n
        \t\t1/4 cup soy sauce\n
        \t\t1/2 cup sugar\n\n\n

\tInstructions\n\n

    1. Measure out rice and rinse in cold water.\n
       Add water according to what the package says\n
       minus ~1/8 cup to account for the rinse.\n\n

    2. Combine spam sauce ingredients in a small\n
       SAUCEPAN. Heat on med-low until sugar\n
       completely dissolves.\n\n

    3. Chop the spam. Cut into 8 slices, then cut\n
       into small cubes.\n\n

    4. Fry the spam cubes in a SAUTEE pan on med-high\n
       until slightly crispy.\n\n

    5. Turn down heat down to medium and add a few\n
       spoonfuls of the spam sauce to taste.\n\n

    6. Assemble bowl: layer of rice, then add ~1/4\n
       of the cooked spam. then the avocado, top with\n
       scallions and optional furikake/sesame seeds.\n\n

    7. Enjoy :)</string>
    <string name="spicyTunaOnigiri">
\tIngredients\n\n

    \t\tNeutral oil\n
    \t\t2 cups white sushi rice\n
    \t\t~1/3 yellow onion, diced\n
    \t\t2 cloves garlic, minced\n
    \t\t~11 oz tuna in a can or pouch\n
    \t\t~2 tbsp Kewpie mayo\n
    \t\t~1-2 tsp Sriracha\n
    \t\t1 package of seaweed snacks\n\n\n

\tInstructions\n\n

    1. Measure out rice and rinse in cold water.\n
       Add water according to what the package says\n
       minus ~1/8 cup to account for the rinse.\n\n

    2. Heat a small amount (~1 tbsp) of neutral oil in a\n
       SAUTE pan. Add onion and cook for a few minutes.\n\n

    3. Pour off excess liquid from tuna can/pouch into\n
       the sink, and put the tuna meat and garlic into\n
       the hot pan. Stir fry for a few minutes.\n\n

    4. Add Sriracha to the pan and cook for a couple\n
       more minutes.\n\n

    5. Remove tuna mix from heat and let cool a bit.\n\n

    6. Once the tuna mix is somewhat cool, add Kewpie\n
       mayo. Add Kewpie and Sriracha to taste.\n\n

    7. Assemble the rice balls. Using the onigiri mold,\n
       add a thin layer of rice to the bottom. Then\n
       spoon a small heap of tune mix to the of the rice.\n
       Then add another layer of rice. Then close the\n
       mold and push together.\n\n

    8. Carefully wrap a seaweed snack around the bottom\n
       of each rice ball.\n\n

    9. Enjoy :)</string>

    <string name="chocolate">
\tIngredients\n

    \t\t\t\tButter and flour for coating and dusting the cake pan\n
    \t\t\t\t3 cups all-purpose flour\n
    \t\t\t\t3 cups granulated sugar\n
    \t\t\t\t1 1/2 cups unsweetened cocoa powder\n
    \t\t\t\t1 tablespoon baking soda\n
    \t\t\t\t1 1/2 teaspoons baking powder\n
    \t\t\t\t1 1/2 teaspoons salt\n
    \t\t\t\t4 large eggs\n
    \t\t\t\t1 1/2 cups buttermilk\n
    \t\t\t\t1 1/2 cups warm water\n
    \t\t\t\t1/2 cup vegetable oil\n
    \t\t\t\t2 teaspoons vanilla extract\n\n

Chocolate Cream Cheese Buttercream Frosting\n\n

    \t\t\t\t1 1/2 cups butter softened\n
    \t\t\t\t8 oz cream cheese softened\n
    \t\t\t\t1 1/2 cups unsweetened cocoa powder\n
    \t\t\t\t3 teaspoons vanilla extract\n
    \t\t\t\t7-8 cups powdered sugar\n
    \t\t\t\tabout 1/4 cup milk as needed\n\n

Instructions\n
The Most Amazing Chocolate Cake\n\n

    1. Preheat oven to 350 degrees Fahrenheit.\n
    Butter three 9-inch cake rounds.\n
    Dust with flour and tap out the excess.\n\n

    2. Mix together flour, sugar, cocoa, baking soda, baking powder,\n
    and salt in a stand mixer using a low speed until combined.\n\n

    3. Add eggs, buttermilk, warm water, oil, and vanilla.\n
    Beat on a medium speed until smooth.\n
    This should take just a couple of minutes.\n\n

    4. Divide batter among the three pans. I found that it took just\n
    over 3 cups of the batter to divide it evenly.\n\n

    5. Bake for 30-35 minutes in a 350 degree oven until a\n
    toothpick inserted into the center comes out clean.\n\n

    6. Cool on wire racks for 15 minutes and then turn out the\n
    cakes onto the racks and allow to cool completely.\n\n

    7. Frost with your favorite frosting and enjoy!\n\n

Chocolate Cream Cheese Buttercream Frosting\n\n

    1. In a large bowl, beat together butter and cream cheese until\n
    fluffy. Use a hand mixer or stand mixer for best results\n\n

    2. Add in cocoa powder and vanilla extract. Beat until combined.\n\n

    3. Beat in powdered sugar, 1 cup at a time.\n
    Add milk as necessary to make a spreadable consistency.\n
    The frosting should be very thick and will thicken even more\n
    if refrigerated.\n\n

    Courtesy of Rachel Farnsworth at The Stay at Home Chef\n
https://thestayathomechef.com/the-most-amazing-chocolate-cake</string>
    <string name="cheesecake">
\tIngredients\n
For the crust\n\n

    \t\t\t\t2 cups (200 g) graham cracker crumbs, about 2 sleeves\n
    \t\t\t\t¼ cup (50g) granulated sugar\n
    \t\t\t\t6 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted\n\n

For the filling\n\n

    \t\t\t\t32 ounces (904 g) cream cheese, room temperature\n
    \t\t\t\t1 ⅓ cups (266 g) granulated sugar\n
    \t\t\t\t1 cup (227 g) sour cream, room temperature\n
    \t\t\t\t1 tablespoon vanilla extract\n
    \t\t\t\t¼ teaspoon salt\n
    \t\t\t\t4 large eggs, room temperature, lightly beaten\n\n

For the sauce\n\n

    \t\t\t\t16 ounces (400 g) whole strawberries, diced\n
    \t\t\t\t2 tablespoons cornstarch\n
    \t\t\t\t1 cup (200 g) granulated sugar\n
    \t\t\t\t2 teaspoons vanilla extract\n
    \t\t\t\t⅛ teaspoon salt\n
    \t\t\t\t2 cups (334 g) finely chopped strawberries\n\n

Instructions\n
Make the crust\n\n

    1. Move the oven rack to the lower third position and\n
    heat the oven to 350°F. Wrap the outer bottom of a 9-inch\n
    springform pan tightly with aluminum foil.\n\n

    2. Combine the graham cracker crumbs, sugar, and melted\n
    butter. Press the crumb mixture into the bottom and about\n
    2-inches up the sides of the pan. Bake for 10 minutes.\n
    Set aside to cool while you make the filling.\n\n

Make the filling\n\n

    1. Reduce the oven temperature to 300ºF.\n\n

    2. In a large mixing bowl beat the cream cheese with an\n
    electric mixer until smooth and creamy, about 1 minute.\n\n

    3. Add the sugar and sour cream, beat until well combined.\n
    Add the vanilla and salt, beat on low speed until smooth.\n\n

    4. Using a silicone spatula, gently stir in the eggs just\n
    until combined. Pour the batter over the prepared crust.\n\n

    5. Fill a roasting pan with a few inches of boiling water\n
    and place the cheesecake in the center.\n\n

    6. Bake for 1 hour, OR until the edges are set and the center is\n
    slightly jiggly. Turn the oven off, leave the cheesecake\n
    in the water bath in the oven for another hour.\n\n

    7. Remove the cheesecake from the water bath and place it on a\n
    wire rack. Run a small knife around the outer edge of the\n
    cheesecake to loosen it from the pan and leave it to cool\n
    completely.\n\n

Make the sauce\n\n

    1. Add the diced strawberries and cornstarch to the bowl\n
    of a food processor and process until smooth.\n
    Transfer to a medium saucepan and add the sugar.\n\n

    2. Cook over medium heat, stirring constantly until thickened,\n
    about 15 minutes.\n\n

    3. Remove from heat and stir in the vanilla, salt, and chopped\n
    strawberries. Set aside to cool for about 40 minutes,\n
    stirring occasionally.\n\n

    4. Spread the topping evenly over the cheesecake and\n
    refrigerate for at least 4 hours, preferably overnight.\n\n

    5. Remove the sides of the pan just before serving.\n\n

    Courtesy of Jen Sobjack at Baked by an Introvert\n
https://www.bakedbyanintrovert.com/strawberry-cheesecake/#mv-creation-422-jtr</string>
    <string name="birthday">
\tIngredients\n
For the Cake Layers\n\n

    \t\t\t\t2 cups all-purpose flour, spooned into measuring cup and\n
    \t\t\t\tleveled-off with back edge of knife\n
    \t\t\t\t2 teaspoons baking powder\n
    \t\t\t\t1/4 teaspoon salt\n
    \t\t\t\t12 tablespoons (1-1/2 sticks) unsalted butter, softened\n
    \t\t\t\t1-1/2 cups granulated sugar\n
    \t\t\t\t6 large egg whites, at room temperature\n
    \t\t\t\t3/4 cup whole milk, at room temperature\n
    \t\t\t\t1-1/2 teaspoons vanilla extract\n
    \t\t\t\t1/2 teaspoon almond extract\n\n

For the Buttercream\n\n

    \t\t\t\t12 tablespoons (1-1/2 sticks) unsalted butter, softened\n
    \t\t\t\t4 ounces cream cheese, at room temperature\n
    \t\t\t\t6 cups confectioners\' sugar\n
    \t\t\t\t3 teaspoons vanilla extract\n
    \t\t\t\tPinch salt\n\n

Instructions\n
For the Cake\n\n

    Position a rack in the middle of the oven and preheat to 350°F.\n
    Spray two 8-inch cake pans with nonstick cooking spray.\n
    Cut two 8-inch rounds of parchment paper and line the bottom\n
    of each pan; spray the paper with nonstick spray.\n
    (To measure the parchment paper, just trace the bottom of\n
    the pan.)\n\n

    In a medium bowl, whisk together the flour,\n
    baking powder, and salt.\n\n

    Place the butter and sugar in the bowl of a heavy-duty mixer\n
    fitted with the paddle attachment and beat on medium speed\n
    for about 5 minutes, or until very soft and light.\n
    Beat in the vanilla and almond extracts.\n\n

    Meanwhile, whisk together the egg whites and milk by hand\n
    in a medium bowl until just combined.\n
    Reduce the mixer speed to low and beat in one-quarter of the\n
    flour mixture, then one-third of the milk mixture, stopping and\n
    scraping down the bowl and beater after each addition.\n
    Beat in another quarter of the flour, then another third of the\n
    milk mixture. Scrape again. Repeat with another quarter of the\n
    flour and the remaining milk mixture; scrape.\n
    Finally, beat in the remaining flour mixture.\n\n

    Scrape the bowl with a large rubber spatula.\n
    Don\'t worry if the batter looks a little grainy.\n
    Pour the batter into the prepared cake pans and\n
    smooth the tops.\n\n

    Bake the cakes for 30-35 minutes, until they are well risen\n
    and firm and a toothpick inserted into the center emerges clean.\n
    Cool the cakes in the pans on rack for 5 minutes,\n
    then unmold onto rack to finish cooling right side up\n
    (keep parchment paper underneath cake layers so they don\'t\n
    stick to rack). When cake layers are completely cool,\n
    transfer to cake plate and frost with vanilla buttercream.\n
    (I always flip the bottom layer of the cake so that the\n
    domed side is facing down and touching the plate.\n
    That way, the surface that you\'re icing is flat and will\n
    minimize any separating between the two layers when you\n
    put the other layer on top of it.)\n\n

For the Vanilla Buttercream\n\n

    In the bowl of an electric mixer, cream the butter and\n
    cream cheese until creamy and well combined.\n\n

    Gradually add the confectioners\' sugar,\n
    then beat in the vanilla and salt.\n
    If the frosting is too thick, add 1-2 tablespoons of milk or cream.\n\n

    Courtesy of Jenn Segal at Once Upon a Chef\n
https://www.onceuponachef.com/recipes/vanilla-birthday-cake-with-old-fashioned-vanilla-buttercream.html</string>
    <string name="key_lime">
\tIngredients\n
For the Crust\n\n

    \t\t\t\t1-1/2 cups finely crushed graham cracker crumbs,\n
    from about 12 whole graham crackers\n
    \t\t\t\t1/3 cup packed light brown sugar\n
    \t\t\t\t4 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted\n\n

For the Filling\n\n

    \t\t\t\tTwo 14-oz cans sweetened condensed milk\n
    \t\t\t\t1 cup plain Greek yogurt (2% or whole milk)\n
    \t\t\t\t1 tablespoon grated lime zest\n
    \t\t\t\t3/4 cup fresh lime juice\n\n

For the Topping\n\n

    \t\t\t\t1 cup cold heavy cream\n
    \t\t\t\t2 tablespoons confectioners\' sugar\n
    \t\t\t\t1 teaspoon grated lime zest\n
    \t\t\t\t8 to 10 thin lime slices\n\n

Instructions\n
For the Crust\n\n

    Preheat oven to 375 °F and set an oven rack in the middle\n
    position.\n\n

    In a medium bowl, combine the graham cracker crumbs,\n
    brown sugar, and melted butter; stir with a fork first,\n
    and then your hands until the mixture is well combined.\n
    Using your fingers and the bottom of a glass or dry\n
    measuring cup, press the crumbs firmly into the bottom and\n
    up the sides of a 9 x 1.5-inch pie pan.\n
    The crust should be about ¼-inch thick.\n
    (Tip: do the sides first.)\n\n

    Bake for 10 minutes, until just slightly browned.\n
    Let the crust cool on a wire rack.\n\n

For the Filling\n\n

    Lower the oven temperature to 350°F.\n\n

    In a large bowl, whisk together the sweetened condensed milk,\n
    yogurt, lime zest, and lime juice.\n
    Pour the thick mixture into the warm graham cracker crust.\n
    Bake for 15 minutes, until the filling is almost set;\n
    it should wobble a bit. Let cool at room temperature for\n
    30 minutes, then place in the refrigerator to chill thoroughly,\n
    about 3 hours.\n\n

For the Topping\n\n

    In the bowl of an electric mixer, beat the heavy cream until\n
    soft peaks form. Add the confectioners\' sugar and beat until\n
    medium peaks form. Top the pie with the whipped cream.\n
    Decorate with the lime zest and lime slices.\n
    Store the pie in the refrigerator until ready to serve.\n
    Slice the pie into wedges, wiping your knife clean between\n
    slices, and serve cold.\n\n

Courtesy of Jenn Segal at Once Upon a Chef\n
https://www.onceuponachef.com/recipes/key-lime-pie.html</string>
    <string name="apple">
\tIngredients\n

    \t\t\t\t3 pounds good cooking apples such as Granny Smith,\n
    \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tJonagold, Golden Delicious, Fuji, or Braeburn\n
    \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t(about 6 to 8 apples, depending on the size\n
    \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tof your apples and the size of your pie dish)\n
    \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t1 tablespoon lemon juice or apple cider vinegar\n
    \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t(to toss with the sliced apples so they don\'t\n
    \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tbrown as you slice them)\n
    \t\t\t\t1/2 cup to 2/3 cup sugar, depending on how\n
    \t\t\t\tsweet you like your pie\n
    \t\t\t\t3 tablespoons all-purpose flour for thickening\n
    \t\t\t\t1/2 teaspoon cinnamon\n
    \t\t\t\t1/4 teaspoon ground allspice\n
    \t\t\t\t1/4 teaspoon ground nutmeg\n
    \t\t\t\t1 tablespoon brandy (Optional. By the way,\n
    \t\t\t\tif you have Calvados apple brandy, use it!)\n
    \t\t\t\t1 teaspoon vanilla extract\n
    \t\t\t\t1 recipe double crust sour cream pie dough,\n
    \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tOR all-butter crust, OR your favorite pie crust\n
    \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\trecipe\n\n

    \t\t\t\tFor the egg wash:\n\n
    \t\t\t\t1 large egg yolk\n
    \t\t\t\t1 tablespoon cream\n\n

Method\n\n

    1. Peel, core, and slice the apples\n
    Peel, core and slice or roughly chop the apples into 1/4-inch\n
    to 1/2-inch slices or chunks.\n\n

    As you cut your apple slices, add them to a large bowl and\n
    sprinkle them with a little lemon juice or apple cider vinegar to\n
    help keep them from turning brown.\n\n

    2. Make the apple pie filling\n
    Combine sugar, flour and spices (allspice, nutmeg, cinnamon)\n
    in a bowl. Add the flour mixture to the apple slices and use your\n
    hands to distribute the flour through the apples so they are well\n
    coated.\n\n

    Then sprinkle with brandy and vanilla extract and stir to\n
    coat all the apples.\n\n

    3. Prepare oven\n
    Place one oven rack in the lowest position and put a large\n
    rimmed baking sheet on it (to catch any drippings from the\n
    pie.) Position a second rack the next rung up (still in the\n
    lower third of the oven) and preheat to 375°F.\n\n

    4. Roll out the dough and line bottom pie plate\n
    Remove one disk of pie dough from the refrigerator. Let sit at\n
    room temperature for 5-10 minutes. Place disk on a lightly\n
    floured, clean, flat surface. Using a rolling pin, roll out the pie\n
    dough to a 12-inc circle, about 1/8 of an inch thick.\n\n

    As you roll out the dough, check to make sure it isn\'t sticking.\n
    If and when it starts to stick, gently lift it up and sprinkle a\n
    little more flour on the table surface or on the pie dough to keep\n
    the dough from sticking.\n\n

    Gently place the rolled out dough onto a 9-inch pie plate. Press\n
    down to line the pie dish with the dough.\n\n

    5. Place apple slices on top of the bottom crust\n
    Arrange the apple slices in the dough-lined pie plate. Mound the\n
    apples in the center.\n\n

    6. Roll out top crust, place over apples, trim and crimp edges\n
    Roll out the second disk of dough, again to 12-inches. Gently\n
    place the second round of pie dough over the apples. Trim\n
    excess dough with kitchen shears, leaving a 3/4 inch overhang\n
    from the edges of the pie pan.\n\n

    Fold the dough under itself so that the edge of the fold comes\n
    right to the edge of the pan. Press the top and bottom dough\n
    rounds together as you flute edges using thumb and forefinger\n
    or press with a fork.\n\n

    7. Brush with egg wash, cut vents\n
    Place egg yolk and cream in a small bowl and use a fork to stir\n
    until well combined. Use a pastry brush to brush the egg wash\n
    over the top and fluted edges of the pie. Use a sharp knife to\n
    cut slits in the top of the pie crust for steam vents.\n\n

    8. Bake\n
    Place pie on oven rack centered over the baking sheet on the\n
    rack below it to catch any drippings. Bake the pie at 375°F\n
    until crust begins to lightly brown, about 20 minutes, then reduce\n
    heat to 350°F.\n\n

    Bake until crust is golden and juices are bubbling, anywhere\n
    from an additional 45 minutes to an hour, depending on the type\n
    of apples you are using. (About halfway through baking check to\n
    make sure the pie isn\'t browning too much. When it\'s nicely\n
    browned, tent the pie with a large piece of aluminum foil to keep\n
    the pie from browning further.)\n\n

    9. Let cool\n
    Transfer the apple pie to a rack to cool for at least 1 hour.\n
    Serve slightly warm or at room temperature. Great with a side\n
    of vanilla ice cream.\n\n

    Courtesy of Elise Bauer at Simply Recipes\n
https://www.simplyrecipes.com/recipes/old_fashioned_apple_pie/</string>
    <string name="mac">
\tIngredients\n

    \t\t1 (1 pound) box cellentani, cavatappi, or elbow macaroni\n
    \t\t4 cups chicken broth or garlic broth\n
    \t\t4 tablespoons (1/2 stick) salted butter\n
    \t\t4 cups (1 pound) shredded sharp Cheddar cheese\n
    \t\t1/4 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n
    \t\Optional:\n
    \t\t2-4 ounces cream cheese, cut into chunky cubes\n
    \t\t1 (5.2 ounce) package Boursin spread, cut into cubes\n
    \t\t1 teaspoon Dijon mustard\n
    \t\t1 tablespoon hot sauce\n
    \t\tA few splashes milk or cream for additional smoothness\n\n

\tInstructions\n
    \t\t1. Add the macaroni, broth, butter to the Instant Pot.\n\t\t\tStir well\n
    \t\t2. Put the lid on the pot, sealed, and hit "Manual" or\n\t\t\t"Pressure Cook"
           High Pressure and set for 6 minutes\n
    \t\t3. Quick release and open lid when finished. When the\n
    \t\t\tlid comes off, there will be a lot of liquid in the pot-but\n
    \t\t\tthis is exactly what we want as it will serve as the base\n
    \t\t\tfor the sauce!\n
    \t\t4. Add the Parmesan, cheddar, cream cheese or Boursin,\n
        \t\t\tmustard (if using), and hot sauce (if using). Stir until\n
        \t\t\tit gets creamy-a few minutes! It may appear runny at\n
        \t\t\tfirst, but once you let it set for a few minutes after\n
        \t\t\tstirring, it will really begin to thicken up good
    \t\tEnjoy :)</string>
</resources>